Hello everyone, here I have the Galaxy S25s
One of the most important features of this phone is that it's thin and light
But more importantly, it's big, so when you hold it, it feels different than most of the phones I have
The screen of the Galaxy S25s is 6.7 inches, which is the same size as the Galaxy S25 Plus
But because it's thinner and lighter, it's great to hold
The thickness is 5.8mm and the weight is 163g
This is the thinnest Galaxy S series so far
However, I still recommend you to go to the store and try it
Because you look at the picture, it's really thin
But when you hold it, the combination of thin, light and big
So it feels great, it's very different, it's very special
In addition, you can see that on the Galaxy S25s, there is a slight change in design
Compared to the S25 series, this camera holder has a circle around it
I think this design is beautiful and it reminds me a bit of the S21 series
Although the design is not very similar to the S21 series, it has a point on the back, it's not too straight
Here I can't see the connection, because all of them have a protective wire like this
Samsung also said that the screen of the Galaxy S25s is coated with a glass layer called Corning Gorilla Ceramic Glass 2
This is a layer of glass that increases the screen resolution compared to the previous series
However, when I compare it with the Galaxy S25 Ultra that I have here
I don't think it has a reflective layer like the S25 Ultra
Its screen and display quality are similar to the S25 Plus
The screen is very thin, the screen is as thin as the Ultra, it looks very beautiful
And it's not just thin, it's even thinner, so this part is good
The main camera is 200 megapixels, the telephoto camera is not available
There is an Ultra Wide camera with a resolution of 12 megapixels and autofocus
In general, the ability to take pictures of a phone like this is clearly thinner than the normal series
So we have to sacrifice the telephoto camera
I think for customers who like this kind of phone, especially those who like a fashionable, thin, and attractive phone
This is not a big problem
In addition, the battery of the Galaxy S25s is 3915mAh, which is smaller than other Galaxy S series
But it's thin, I accept it
As for the power, it still has the Snapdragon 8 Elite 4 Galaxy
This is a chip that has been used for the entire Galaxy S25 series
The Galaxy S25s is also the same
In short, what do we need to care about the Galaxy S25s?
Thin, light, very comfortable to hold
But it still ensures that your phone is still a powerful machine, it's not a mid-range
It's still a very high-end machine, it's still very good
As for the Galaxy AI features, the Galaxy S25s has all of them
Nothing less than the normal Galaxy S25 or even the Galaxy S25 Ultra
The chip and the life together, and especially the many Galaxy AI features, are all based on the cloud
So the fact that the Galaxy S25s supports all of the Galaxy AI features is a must
The functions such as removing objects from the image, or subtracting, subtracting, or the AI in the memory are all complete
When I have this official version of the machine, I will hold it and experience it more carefully for you to see
At the moment, at the launch event, it's just like this
This time, Samsung also officially released the Galaxy Ring, which is a smart ring that specializes in health monitoring
Previously, this ring was not sold in Vietnam, now it is officially sold
When you buy this Galaxy Ring, you will have a set of rings to try on many sizes of your hand
If you see which size is suitable, you will buy it
Among the colors sold here, there are silver, black, and even yellow
As for the Galaxy ring
One of the most important function of this ring is to monitor your health
It's similar to a smart watch
But the ring is smaller and you can wear it on your wrist for a longer time
That's the purpose of these rings
I'm not a ring wearer myself, so I'm going to give you some tips
If I can borrow this Galaxy Ring and test it for a long time, I'll think about it later
When you charge it, you'll get a case like this
I'll put a picture of it
It's both a charging case and a storage case
If I want to test it more, I'll have to hold it outside
Because I can only hold the ring here
I know it's beautiful and light
The ring is made of titanium
If I want to test it more, I'll borrow it outside and think about it later
Thank you and see you again